<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arif&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Arif&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Simple Javascript Theme Switcher Using Cookie</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/simple-javascript-theme-switcher-using-cookie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/simple-javascript-theme-switcher-using-cookie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As people become more aware of their eye health, dark theme has become so popular it almost becomes the standard color scheme for digital content nowadays, including blogs and static sites. Theme switching capability also becomes popular to be implemented on said media.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are many ways to implement a theme switcher. The most common way is by having two separate CSS files, loading both CSS at the same time, then using JavaScript to modify the &lt;code&gt;class&lt;/code&gt; properties of all elements. So, for example, when the user triggers the script to use dark theme, then each element&amp;rsquo;s &lt;code&gt;class&lt;/code&gt; properties will be appended with something like &lt;code&gt;-dark&lt;/code&gt;; light theme will modify it to &lt;code&gt;-light&lt;/code&gt;. But, what if I told you there is a simpler approach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My New Laptop: ASUS ZenBook S16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/my-new-laptop-asus-zenbook-s16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/my-new-laptop-asus-zenbook-s16/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just bought a new laptop, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.asus.com/laptops/for-home/zenbook/asus-zenbook-s-16-um5606/&#34;&gt;ASUS ZenBook S16&lt;/a&gt;. This is intended to be my backup workstation in case my main computer gets broken or I&amp;rsquo;m traveling and somehow need to work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-did-i-choose-this-laptop&#34;&gt;Why did I choose this laptop&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Honestly, it&amp;rsquo;s because I got a neat deal in my local online store (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.blibli.com/&#34;&gt;Blibli&lt;/a&gt;), around IDR 24 million / USD 1,493 at the time I bought it. So, it&amp;rsquo;s not purely because I really like or want this laptop. I did, however, spend time researching this laptop before I bought it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Include Subfolders in Windows 11 Wallpaper Slideshow</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/include-subfolders-in-windows-11-wallpaper-slideshow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/include-subfolders-in-windows-11-wallpaper-slideshow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Windows 11 has a feature that enables us to change desktop wallpapers at specified intervals. However, by default, it only scans pictures in the root directory of our choice and doesn&amp;rsquo;t allow us to include its subfolders. To change this, we need to make changes to the Windows 11 system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;install-link_nto1-powershell-script&#34;&gt;Install link_Nto1 PowerShell Script&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;link_Nto1 is a PowerShell script that helps us create hard/symbolic links to all files of a specified source folder inside a specified destination folder. In the context of this post, we can specify our wallpapers folder (which contains subfolders), and then the script will make symbolic links to all pictures in its subfolders. The script then places those symbolic links in certain folders which we specify, then we can make Windows 11 use that folder instead of our original wallpapers folder.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi I&amp;rsquo;m Arif. This is where I write my thoughts and something I stumbled upon when I&amp;rsquo;m working and tinkering.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also see some of &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/projects&#34;&gt;my projects&lt;/a&gt; that I made.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks for visiting and reading!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are my projects that I worked on in my spare time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
